JOSEPH E. PERSICO PAPERS (APAP030) 1910-2003
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
1976 October 20 Washington, D.C., Remarks, J. Braden Consumer Conference
1976 October 20 Washington, D.C., Q & A, J. Braden Consumer Conference
1976 October 26 Washington, D.C., One Week To Go
1976 October 27 Franklin Square, NY, Press Release, Franklin Square
1976 October 27 Franklin Square, NY, Senior Citizens Rally
1976 October 27 Franklin Square, NY, Press Conference, Senior Citizen Rally
1976 October 27 Franklin Square, NY, Women's Tea Rally
1976 October 27 Hempstead, NY, Hofstra University
1976 October 27 Hempstead, NY, Community Leader Dinner
1976 October 27 Island Park, NY, Island Park Republican Rally
1976 October 27 Long Island, NY, Press Release, Ford-Dole Campaign
1976 November 5 Washington, D.C., Exchange of Remarks, between WAR & Ford
1976 November 12 Williamsburg, VA, Remarks, Williamsburg Foundation
1976 November 16 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Conference on Productivity
1976 November 16 Washington, D.C., Text of Remarks, Republican Eagles
1976 November 16 Washington, D.C., Republican Eagles
1976 November 16 Washington, D.C., 10 Outstanding Young Women
1976 November 16 Washington, D.C., Defense Advisory Committee
1976 November 18 Williamsburg, VA, North Atlantic Treaty
1976 November 18 Williamsburg, VA, Remarks, North Atlantic Treaty
1976 November 21 Pocantico Hills, NY, Exchange of Remarks, J. D. Rockefeller Estate
1976 November 30 New York City, NY, China Institute in America
1976 December 8 Washington, D.C., Georgetown University
1976 December 9 Washington, D.C., Exchange of Remarks, The President, Rockefeller, and J.B. Connally
1976 December 14 Washington, D.C., Political Science Association
1976 December 14 Washington, D.C., Remarks, National Capital Area Political Science Association, Campaign Spending
1976 December 16 Washington, D.C., Press Conference, Director of Office of Science and Technology, Ford
1976 December 18 Washington, D.C., Remarks, US Senate
Scope and Content Information
The collected papers of Joseph Persico focus on his careers as a political speechwriter and as a full-time author. His speeches from the 1960s include his work for both New York State Commissioner of Health, Hollis Ingraham, and New York State Governor, Nelson Rockefeller. Press releases and transcripts associated with the speeches are also present in the Persico files. Nelson Rockefeller's Messages to the Legislature and "Quotes on Issues" during the late 1960s and early 1970s have been filed in Series 1 with Persico's speeches. The Chronological Index to Press Releases, Speeches, and Transcripts Written for Nelson A. Rockefeller was transcribed by Kevin Lawyer from the handwritten original provided by the donor. The index covers the years 1964-1976.
The author's publications files include manuscripts, correspondence, screenplays, interviews for The Imperial Rockefeller, and research notes. For Persico's Piercing the Reich, several folders hold parts of a single OSS (Office of Strategic Services) War Report from 1949, detailing OSS action in Europe, Africa, and Asia during World War II. For Nuremberg: Infamy on Trial, the author's files contain a draft of the work and research material including photos from the Holocaust and the Nuremberg Trials.
The texts, drafts, news clippings, correspondence, and other supporting material is available for speeches and other non-book writings of Persico. Among the author's correspondence is an exchange with movie director John Huston who Persico interviewed for an article in American Heritage. Note that correspondence can be found throughout the collection. For example, references to Persico's publications will be found in both the general correspondence files and specific publications' series. An attempt was made to retain the original filing system of the creator with the most recent accessions, but previous arrangement divided some of the correspondence into professional and personal folders.
The material received from the donor in May 2006 is not yet arranged and described in this finding aid. Contact Department staff for further information.
Additional material collected and created by Persico during the writing of Piercing the Reich was deposited by Persico at the Hoover Institution Library and Archives at Stanford University. The finding aid for this material is available online through the Online Archive of California. Persico also gave additional material related to his book Edward R. Murrow: An American Original to the Edward R. Murrow Center of Public Diplomacy at Tufts University.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized as follows:
Series 1: New York State Government Career, 1910-1981
Sub-series 1: Speeches, Press Releases, and Transcripts, 1965-1976
Sub-series 2: Subject Files, 1947-1976
Sub-series 3: Newsclippings, 1968-1975
Series 2: Publications, ca. 1930s-2001
Sub-series 1: Piercing the Reich, 1940-1979
Sub-series 2: Columbus, ca. 1980-1990
Sub-series 3: My Enemy, My Brother, 1977
Sub-series 4: The Spiderweb, 1975-1983
Sub-series 5: Edward R. Murrow: An American Original, 1984-2001
Sub-series 6: Casey: From the OSS to the CIA, 1989-1991
Sub-series 7: Teacher, 1989-1990
Sub-series 8: The Imperial Rockefeller, ca. 1970s-1985
Sub-series 9: Nuremberg: Infamy on Trial, ca. 1930-2001
Sub-series 10: Roosevelt's Secret War: FDR and World War II Espionage, 2001
Series 3: Speeches and Writings, 1958-2003
Sub-series 1: Speeches, 1975-2002
Sub-series 2: Writings, 1958-2003
Series 4: Correspondence, 1960-2002
Series 5: Biographical, 1958-2001
.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by Joseph E. Persico in 1984. The Department received additional material from Mr. Persico in August 1997, May 1998, December 1999, December 2003, and May 2006.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Subject and Genre Headings
Women; State University of New York SUNY, Central Administration; Public Servants; Military and Armed Conflict; Medicine and Health Care; Education; Albany, New York; Casey, William J.; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979.; Ford, Gerald R., 1913-2006.; Murrow, Edward R.; United States. Central Intelligence Agency.; United States. Office of Strategic Services.; Generals -- United States.; Gettysburg Campaign, 1863.; Government and the press -- New York (State); Intelligence officers -- United States.; Nuremberg Trial of Major German War Criminals, Nuremberg, Germany, 1945-1946.; New York (State) -- Politics and government.; United States -- Politics and government.
Container List
- New York State Government Career, 1910-1981; 1; 9.8
  This series contains Persico's public papers, including press releases, transcripts of press conferences, television and radio interviews, and drafts of speeches written for New York State Commissioner of Health Hollis Ingraham and Nelson A. Rockefeller (1964-1977). Press releases and transcripts associated with the speeches are also present in the Persico files. Rockefeller's Messages to the Legislature and "Quotes on Issues" during the late 1960s and early 1970s have been filed in this series with the speeches written by Persico. Several boxes contained in this series are subject files relating personally to the author, his work, and to Nelson Rockefeller. A partial index to speeches is available in the Department of Special Collections and Archives. Consult a staff member for details. Also included in this series are subject files and news clippings. While most of these documents date from 1964-1977, some related materials date from 1947-1981.
  The Chronological Index to Press Releases, Speeches, and Transcripts Written for Nelson A. Rockefeller was transcribed by Kevin Lawyer from the handwritten original provided by the donor. The index covers the years 1964-1976.
  - Speeches, Press Releases, and Transcripts, 1965-1976; 1.1
    - Persico's Notepads, ca. 1966-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1964 July-1965 October (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1966 January-1966 September (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1966 October-1966 November (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1968 January-1968 March (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1968 April-1968 June (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1968 July-1968 December (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1969 January-1969 May (Box 1A, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1969 June-1969 December (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 January-1970 February (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 March (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 March (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 April (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 April (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 May (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 May (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 June (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 June (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 July (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 August (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 August (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 September (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 September (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 October (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 October (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1970 November (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, 1970 December (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, 1970 December (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, 1970 December (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1971 January (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, 1971 February (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1971 March (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1971 April (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1971 May (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1971 June (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1971 July (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1971 August (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1971 September (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1971 October (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1971 November (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1971 December (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 January (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 February (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 March (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 April (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 May (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 June (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 July (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 August (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 September (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 October (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 November (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 November (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, 1972 November (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 November (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 November (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, 1972 November (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1972 December (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 January (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 January (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, 1973 February (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 March (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 April (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 May (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 June (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 July (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 August (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 September (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 September (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 October (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 October (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 November (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1973 December (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1974 January (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1974 February (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1974 February (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1974 March (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1974 March (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, 1974 April (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1974 May (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Speeches and Transcripts, 1974 June (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Speeches and Transcripts, 1974 July (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Speeches and Transcripts, 1974 August (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1974 September (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Speeches and Transcripts, 1974 October (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1975 January (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1975 February-1975 May (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1975 June-1975 August (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1975 September (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1975 October (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1975 October (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1975 November (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1975 December (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 January (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 February (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 March (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 April (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 May (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 June (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 July (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 August (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 September (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 September (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 October (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 October (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 November (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, Press Releases and Transcripts, 1976 December (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Messages to Legislature, 1967-1974 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Speech Index, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Speech Index, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Speech Index, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Speech Index, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Speech Index, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Speech Index, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Speech Index, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Speech Index, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Speech Index, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Speech Index, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller's (NAR) Quotes on Issues, (used through 1973) (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Letters, 1970-1976 (Box 17, Folder 1-3)
    - Memos, 1967-1971 (Box 17, Folder 4-10)
    - Memos, 1972-1976; Undated (Box 17A, Folder 1-6)
  - Subject Files, 1947-1976; 1.2
    - Subject File Listings (Composition Notebook), 1970s (Box 18, Folder 1A)
    - Abortion, 1970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Acupuncture, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Admiral's House, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Adirondack State Park, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture, 1970-1973 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Administration, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Arts, 1969-1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Attica, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Basic Documents, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Blacks, 1975; Undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Buckley, 1968-1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - CIA Commission, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Campaign 1964, 1964-1976 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Campaign 1966 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Campaign 1968, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Campaign 1970, 1970-1975 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Campaign 1972 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Campaign 1976, 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Campaign Spending, 1966-1976 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - College, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Confirmation, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Coordinator of Inter American Affairs, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Costa Rica, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Critical Choices, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Daily Schedules, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - De Toqueville, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Death Penalty, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Defense, Undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1966-1970 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Draft, Undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Drugs, 1970-1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Dyslexia, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Education, 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Empire State Plaza, 1970-1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Energy Independence Authority, 1975-1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Falconry, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Farmers, Undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Federal Aid, 1964-1976 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Filibuster, 1975; Undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Fine, William F., 1980 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - 'Firsts' in New York State, Undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Food, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Ford, Gerald, 1973-1979 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Garbage Strike, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Goldwater, Barry, 1964-1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Club, Undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Health, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      (including Pollution issues).
    - Historic Preservation, 1972-1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - History, 1972-1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Humor, 1964-1976; Undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Intern Interview, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Italian Americans, 1955-1973 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Kendall, Kathleen E., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1968-1980 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Latin America, 1961-1969 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Argentina, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Barbados, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Bolivia, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Brazil, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Columbia, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Costa Rica, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Dominican Republic, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Ecuador, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, El Salvador, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Guatemala, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Guyana, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Haiti, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Honduras, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Jamaica, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Mexico, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Nicaragua, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Panama, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Paraguay, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Peru, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Trinidad-Tobago, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Uruguay, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Venezuela, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Latin American Mission, Receipts, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Lefkowitz, L., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Lincoln, A., Undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Long Island Bridge, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Lottery, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Lubell, S., 1970 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Writing, 1968-1981 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Montesacro, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Monthly Calendars, 1968-1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Nakasian, S., 1968 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - National Caucus of Labor Committees, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Nursing Homes, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Philanthropies, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Pocantico, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Polls, 1968-1974 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Presidency, 1968-1973 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Press, 1970-1975 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Program Papers, ca. 1960s-1970s) (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Mrs. [Happy] Rockefeller, 1969-1976 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., Death, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1958-1979; Undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Rockefeller Family, 1910-1979; Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Photos, 1970s-1981 (mostly Undated) (Box 22, Folder 2)
      (Also see Oversize).
    - Salaries & Bookkeeping Materials, 1968-1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Slote, Les, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Source Speeches, 1963-1976 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Speechwriting, 1968-1976; Undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Staff, 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Swearing In, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Transportation, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Tri-Lateral Commission, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Urban Development Corporation, 1968-1975 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Vice Presidency, 1955-1977 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Viet Nam, 1968-1975 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Watergate, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Women, Undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - White House Staff, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Admiral's House Pamphlet, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Material Pamphlets, 1960s-1970s; Undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Critical Choices for Americans Pamphlets, 1970s (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Ford, Gerald, Pamphlets, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Historic Preservation Pamphlets, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Pocantico Pamphlets, late 1970s; Undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Collection Catalog, Undated (Box 23, Folder 7)